<resources>
    <string name="app_name">SugarHelp</string>
    <string name="recommendations1Break">
         What we choose to eat for breakfast will likely impact our blood sugar levels for the entire day.
         \nHigh-carb/low-fat,or high-fat/low-carb are the ideal combinations for the sake of blood sugar management.
         \n10 to 20 grams of net carbs (total carb minus dietary fiber grams = net carbs).
         \nChoosing foods with a low glycemic Index rating (less likely to spike blood sugar).
         \nAt least 10 grams of protein.
         \nAt least 10 grams of fat.
         \nMany with type 1 diabetes find they need one unit of insulin immediately upon waking to prevent morning blood sugar spikes.
         \nWhat food to eat for breakfast? Here are some healthy recommendations:
         \n1. Eggs
         \n2. Oatmeal
         \n3. Muesli
         \n4. Greek yogurt
         \n5. Omelets
         \n6. French toast or pancakes
         \n7. Cottage cheese
    </string>
    <string name="recommendations2Break">
        Breakfast is an essential meal.
        \nResearch shows that people with diabetes who eat breakfast are less likely to overeat throughout the day.
        \nEating a lower-carb breakfast will minimize the resulting glucose response
        \nand means your blood sugar will be better balanced throughout the day.
        \nWhat food to eat for breakfast? Here are some healthy recommendations:
        \n1. Oatmeal
        \n2. Yogurts and Cottage Cheese
        \n3. Salmon
        \n4. Chia
        \n5. Smoothies
        \n6. Eggs.
            </string>
    <string name="recommendations1Lunch">
        1. Grains, Beans, and Starchy Vegetables (6 or more servings a day)
        \nFoods like bread, grains, beans, rice, pasta,
        \nand starchy vegetables are at the bottom of the pyramid
        \nbecause they should serve as the foundation of your diet.
        \n2. Vegetables (3 – 5 servings a day)
        \nChoose fresh or frozen vegetables without added sauces, fats, or salt.
        \nYou should opt for more dark green and deep yellow vegetables,
        \nsuch as spinach, broccoli, romaine, carrots, and peppers.
        \n3. Fruits (2 – 4 servings a day)
        \n4. Milk(2 – 3 servings a day)
        \n5. Meat and Fish(2 – 3 servings a day)
    </string>
    <string name="recommendations2Lunch">
        1. Salads
        \nSalad should be in regular rotation for lunch. You can create a different salad every day of the week by varying your toppings.
        \nTry grilled chicken, shrimp, or fish, but avoid heaping on a lot of fattening ingredients, such as bacon bits and heavy cheeses.
        \n2. Sandwiches
        \nAs with salads, there are many ways to spice up a sandwich. Start with whole-grain bread or a whole-wheat tortilla.
        \nPick a lean meat, such as turkey, ham,or grilled chicken; layer on your choice of veggies; add mustard,
        \nlow-fat mayonnaise, or hummus to the mix — and you have a filling and tasty lunch.
        \n3. Hearty Soups
        \nSoup can be a good option for lunch, with many healthy choices to consider.
        \nChicken noodle, chicken and rice, and tomato (made without cream) are all good choices.
        \n4. Pasta
        \nAs long as you choose whole-grain pasta, you can eat all types of noodles, such as penne, angel hair, or spaghetti.
        \nTo better control type 2 diabetes, keep these tips in mind:
        \nPick whole-grain bread over white bread.
        \nAvoid fried foods.
        \nIf you are craving a sweet after lunch and fresh fruit just wont do, reach for sugar-free, fat-free frozen yogurt.
        \nBe careful of sorbets and sherbets that are loaded with sugar.
        \nAvoid sugary beverages; drink water and tea instead.
    </string>
    <string name="recommendations1Dinner">
        Less than 20 grams of carbs
        \nMostly carbs with a low glycemic index
        \nAt least 20 grams of protein
        \nSome healthy fat
        \nThis should give you a healthy and balanced dinner that won’t spike your blood sugar.
        \nYou can, of course, make changes to these guidelines if you follow a specific diet (ketogenic diet, plant-based diet, etc.)
    </string>
    <string name="recommendations2Dinner">
        Follow the diabetes food pyramid:
        \nChoose lean protein sources, such as turkey, ham, chicken, lean roast beef, and fish.
        \nEat more grains, beans, and starchy vegetables and less fats, sweets, and alcohol.
        \nIn between, and equally divided, are protein choices, non-starchy vegetables, fruit, and milk and dairy products.
        \nStay away from fatty chips and mayonnaise-based salads, like potato salad. Complement your meal with sliced carrots and celery or fruit salad.
    </string>


</resources>